

## CONTACT



678-464-1635



languageisaliquid@gmail.com



AshleyClaiborne.dev



linkedin.com/in/ashley-claiborne/



github.com/aclai4067

#### **PROJECTS**

#### DAILY BLUEPRINT - FINAL CAPSTONE

A organizational app where users can create to-do lists, set to-do items as priorities, and tag co-workers involved with the to-do items. Features a team view of priorities designed to facilitate stand-up meetings. Also includes a Pomodoro timer to assist users in managing their focus time.

- C#/ASP.NET Core Web Application
- · Database created and modified using SQL Server Management Studio
- ReactJS used for client-side application
- Pomodoro timer powered by JavaScript
- Responsive styling with SASS and Bootstrap



## ONE REASON - FRONT END CAPSTONE

A mindfulness app that encourages the user to enter one reason per day for working toward their goals. Reasons can be public or private. Users can review and support other member's public reasons.

- ReactJS application using full CRUD
- · Routing with react-router-dom
- Utilize Firebase for authentication, data storage, and hosting
- Interchangeable themes created using Sass mixins
- · Navbar and modals created with ReactStrap





github.com/aclai4067/one-reasoncapstone

### EDUCATION

## NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL

Full Stack Wed Development Bootcamp 2019 - 2020

#### GEORGIA STATE UNIVERSITY

BFA in Art Education 2004 - 2008

# **ASHLEY** CLAIBORNE

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### ABOUT

I am a software developer with a background in art, customer service, and international credential evaluations. The realization that web development was the right career path for me was a huge light bulb moment in my professional life. I discovered my predilection for software development while in pursuit of a career that allows for continuous growth, and where my interests in collaboration, research and creative problem solving would be well suited.

I started learning to code using teamtreehouse.com courses and quickly found myself chomping at the bit to enroll in Nashville Software School. I currently work full time in Account Management, while completing Nashville Software School's part-time web development bootcamp on evenings and weekends. I will graduate in August 2020 and am excited to transition into a software development career.

## TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE

#### NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL

#### Software Developer | August 2019 - Present

Full year part-time software development bootcamp focusing on full stack development fundamentals and problem solving.

- Source code version control and Project planning/tracking with Git/GitHub
- JavaScript fundamentals including modular, readable code and reusable components
- Built single-page applications with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript libraries like jQuery, and linting with ESLint
- Built full CRUD applications using ReactJs framework
- Database/API utilizing Firebase, JSON, promises, and axios calls
- Styled applications with CSS, Bootstrap and wrote custom styles with SASS
- Created and modified databases using SQL Server Management Studio,
- Created RESTful APIs with C#/.NET using WebAPI
- Developed console applications and unit tests using C#/.NET
- Collaborated remotely on group projects using Slack and Zoom

## WORK EXPERIENCE

REVSPRING INC (formerly Apex Revenue Technologies and LetterLogic, Inc) Leading provider of consumer communications, billing, and payments solutions that maximize revenue opportunities for healthcare providers.

## Account Manager | January 2017 - Present

- Successfully maintained consistent client experience for over 20 accounts through two company mergers
- · Research and troubleshoot client file errors and statement output issues, and communicate with the client to resolve issues.
- Track client history and projects on multiple platforms, including Spiceworks, Jira, and Salesforce.
- Work closely with development team on letter mapping and script changes
- Knowledgeable on various data types used to create statement output, including pipe delimited, flat text file, print image, csv, Excel, xml, PDF image.

## NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF STATE BOARDS OF ACCOUNTANCY (NASBA)

An association dedicated to serving the 55 state boards of accountancy, which regulate the accountancy profession in the United States of America

# Supervisor, Evaluation Services | May 2016 - January 2017

- · Lead day to day operations for international evaluations staff of 8 evaluators
- Managed work distribution and guided staff in personal goal-setting
- Decision-maker on evaluation policies and requirements criteria
- Created and maintained Excel templates to standardize evaluation output
- Effecitvely balanced leadership role with continued Credential Evaluation duties

## International Credential Evaluator | June 2012 - April 2016

- Team Lead responsible for training, research, and evaluation policies
- Determined authenticity and equivalence of international education programs
- Researched various international educational systems and programs to establish department standards on requirements and educational equivalency.
- · Communicated effectively with applicants and CPA Boards to facilitate evaluations
- Trained over 20 new employees on fraud detection and researching educational system